You can build gorgeous websites with
Claude code and Nano Banana 2, even if
you're starting with zero experience.
But 99% of people don't know how to
build profitable websites, which is why
in this video, I'm going to show you
exactly how to build animated websites
that people pay thousands of dollars
for. I'm a new website intelligence
system that turns viewers into buyers.
And if you don't know who I am, my name
is Jack Roberts. I built and sold my
last tech startup [music] to over 60,000
customers, and I've sold websites like
these for thousands of dollars. And this
is all I do, all day, every day. So,
>> [music]
>> if you haven't already, grab that coffee
and let's dive straight in. Gorgeous
websites can sell for thousands of
dollars using Claude code and the new
Nano Banana 2, stuff that wasn't really
possible previously. And I'm going to
show you exactly how to do it in this
video, but you also need intelligence.
Now, what kind of intelligence do you
need? Well, we need intelligence about
the niche that the website sits in. We
need to be able to analyze what the best
performing businesses in that niche are
actually doing. We need a website that
actually supports our core offer,
whatever that might be. A law firm
versus a HVAC company, completely
different business model. And we can do
all of this using Fire Crawl
intelligence, super exciting technology.
And basically, I'm also going to show
you in this video as well how you can
set up a system to enable your client to
request changes to that very specific
website and how you might want to handle
that if you're selling it. So, by using
Claude code, Nano Banana, and Fire
Crawl, we can do five things. I'm going
to show you exactly how you can scrape a
logo from any website, how you can get
the copy from that website, how you can
get intelligence on competitors and the
top performers in any niche on the
planet systematically, how you can then
actually create a 3D animated hero asset
that makes your website stand out, and
how we can then go ahead and create
something that is pretty exceptional.
And to do this, there's only three
things that we need to do. Step one is
going to be gathering intelligence on
the website in the niche so we can
actually find out what best in class
looks like, then build our beautiful
website all around that. Now, to do
this, we need to pick a niche. I suggest
for this one that we go ahead and we do
something along the lines of pool
cleaners in Texas. So, let's say for
example, we work with a company in pool
cleaners in Texas, or we wanted to work
with these companies directly. What
we're going to do is find a random
website. I found one here that we're
going to use, which is diamondpools.com.
So, we use this as an example to see how
we can take that website into stellar.
This is what it looks like. Cool. So,
now, the first thing we need to do is
basically open up Claude code, which
we're going to use in Anti-Gravity. And
then we're going to bring a pre-packaged
skill that I designed for you, so you
can just literally download it. All the
resources are completely free for you.
Just click the links in the description
down below. So, I'm going to download
Anti-Gravity. That sounds like Spanish.
Check out the video on screen. It runs
through everything that you need to
know. So, within Anti-Gravity, it's
basically software that just called
software. You can click on file in the
top left, come down to open folder, come
down here, click on new folder, and
we'll call this one pool cleaner.
Awesome. Then click on create, and then
click on open. Now we're in the pool
cleaner folder. Yes, we trust the
authors. Now, we want to leverage Claude
code. So, to do that, on the left-hand
side and if you haven't already, you can
just download Claude code so you can
access it with Anti-Gravity. Once that
happens, you'll see this thing appear on
the left. You can just click on that and
have a full conversation with it by
clicking on a new session. Cool.
Alternatively, if you want, you can just
double-click in the middle and then
click on the orange thing at the top.
Now, what we're going to do is download
a skill that I've already pre-built for
you, and then we're going to connect
that to Fire Crawl, which is this
beautiful website here, which is going
to go out and find literally the top
performing pool cleaning websites that
exist in that area. It's going to find
out what do they have in common? What
features do they have? What product is
our website trying to sell? And use all
of that to build us a blueprint for a
really incredible website, and then
we're going to build something
incredibly animated on top of it. So,
let's go ahead and grab the resources.
And again, I'll put this all for you
down below in the description, so you
can just grab it. Let's come over to the
vault and grab this one here. So, we're
looking for this one here, which is
awesome. And all I want you to do is
come here and click on website builder
system. Obviously, it'll be slightly
different for you when you click on it.
Great. And then what I want you to do is
come over here to website builder, click
on this, and literally just download the
entire file together. And it'll download
it as a zip. You can open up your
downloads, just double-click on this guy
like so, and now we've got the website
builder and then Anti-Gravity. Just
click these to get to the document area.
Come back to downloads and just drag
this guy over to the left-hand side and
click on add folder to workspace. And
then we're going to give Claude the
following prompt. Either, I'd like you
to familiarize yourself with the website
builder skill on the left-hand side. I
want you to repeat back to me everything
you're going to do step by step. Once
you've done that, I want you to turn
that into a skill that you yourself are
going to save so I can use it whenever I
want to in the future. And if you ever
find that this Claude code is
misbehaving, you can also click on the
terminal at the top, click on new
terminal, open it up, click enter, and
then essentially down here, what you can
do is just simply come down, bring this
up, type in the word Claude, and then
you can do the exact same prompt here.
It's just in case you ever run into any
issues within the actual interface. And
since this one is struggling a little
bit, what I'm going to do is close this
one down and we're going to use this one
here. We're going to right-click and
then click on panel position and just
put this on the right-hand side. I
always like to keep these things in so
you get a fully 100% realistic
experience of building everything and
that you can crush it. So, within Claude
code, there's only three things that
we're going to do. It's going to be a
process. It's going to study the market,
learn from winners, and build a website
grounded in intelligence. First of all,
it's to gather and understand. We're
going to scrape the entire website that
we're given with the Fire Crawl API.
We're going to build a full picture of
the business, and then we're going to
audit the current messaging, the
strengths, the gaps, so we know what the
starting position is. Again, it isn't
just a gorgeous website, it's got
substance. Then we're going to do
competitive research. We're going to
find the top five competitors ranked by
Google Reviews, Trustpilot, and search
visibility. We're going to scrape each
competitor, their design, content,
branding, logos, and SEO. We're going to
synthesize what all the five winners
have in common and the blueprint of what
actually works in your market. Then
finally, we're going to have a beautiful
print-ready report with competitor
profiles, logos,
and brand colors side by side, SEO
landscape, keyword gaps, and a polished
deliverable that we can actually also
give to the client and in addition to
the website or for your own benefit so
you get a real sense of what everything
exists in your own market. And then what
we're going to say to Claude code is,
"Look, I want you to turn this into a
Claude code skill." And once you've done
that, you can do forward slash and then
you can come down and do website builder
like so, hit enter, and then we can
begin the entire process. Now, the first
thing we're going to need is a Fire
Crawl API. So, let's come ahead and go
ahead and grab this from Fire Crawl. You
can get started right completely for
free. So, let's head over to the
dashboard and literally on the homepage
itself, you can see the API key. So,
we're going to grab this right here.
We're going to skip this for now and
then hit that, but give it basically
back over to Claude code. And then in
Claude code, we're going to give it two
things. One is going to be the Fire
Crawl API key, and then we're also going
to give it the website URL, which for us
is going to be diamondpools.com. We head
back over and give that to Claude. Guys,
and just like that, it's come back and
processed everything without touching a
single thing. And what it's done is
given us a Diamond D Pool Services
Market Intelligence Report. So, this is
an asset that we could give to clients
or just good for us to know
individually, you know what I mean? Oh
my goodness, I'm I'm excited to dive
into this. So, a research driven
analysis of the East Texas Pool Service
Market, competitor profiles, success
patterns, and strategic recommendations
for building a website that wins. Cool.
Executive summary. I love the premium
feel that we've got with this. I think
it's fantastic. So, what do we learn
here? So, you're in a competitive East
Texas Pool Service Market. Here are
these specific niches. Trust signals are
table stakes. Professional photography
wins. Content depth drives SEO. The top
five all showcase real complete project
photos, name designs, galleries, before
and after shots, stock imagery signals,
small operation. How cool is that, by
the way, that you just get to share this
insight? And I get people reaching out
to me very often with, "Jack, I did a
full deep dive analysis on your
business. Here's what you're missing."
It doesn't look like this. I can tell
you that for a fact. It's very obviously
AI generated. This looks like it's had
some care and attention. You know, I
challenge you to tell me the last time
you had something look this good that
came uh for free. Content depth drives
SEO. Winners have service pages, FAQ
section, blog content. Really cool,
really helpful insights. Current website
audit. So, we can come down here.
Strengths, trust what sets us apart, and
critical gaps. Interesting. Duplicate H4
headings. It's done a full SEO review.
Gmail contact address. Interesting. Come
down here. Bottom line, the current site
communicates part-time side gig rather
than professional pool service company.
Then we've got competitor profiles, and
again, it's got all this key information
here, which is cool. It's got all their
Trustpilot reviews. And guys, look at
this. We've even got their color
palettes. How freaking amazing is that?
Then we can zoom out a little bit and
have a quick look over here. Let me just
zoom out so you can see what they do
exceptionally well. Paradise Nails is a
personal touch. Owned by us, name pool
designs. Here's another one. Here's
their reviews, and here's what they do
well. This is amazing. I am genuinely
impressed by this. Genuinely, genuinely
impressed by this. I think this is
fantastic. This is really gorgeous.
Again, I'll add this to the skill for
you so that you're going to get the same
thing. And if you want to show this to
clients to grow your base or whatever,
or you just want to look at it for
yourself, you can do. Really freaking
cool. What they do exceptionally well.
We come down, and we get an idea for the
color palette of everything. And then
we've got the bottom, the winning
blueprint. Page structure is hero strong
headline, service categories, photo
gallery, about us, content patterns. And
now we can use what actually wins. And
here's the crazy thing. This has a
really intelligent algorithm about how
it determines what the top websites are.
We do that based on Google rankings. We
do that based on the reviews. So, we get
and and several other factors that are
inside the uh actual skill. But it'll
identify what the top players are, and
then we can reverse engineer what makes
them so great on their website, which I
think is really freaking cool. Then
we've got the SEO landscape. Look at
this, guys. Here's what they all do.
Here's what you do. This is like the
kind of thing you'd expect off of a paid
off of a paid order. I'm really
impressed with this. Recommended website
structure. Home, services, about, blog,
blah, blah, blah. And then imagine
sending this and be like, "And by the
way, here you freaking go. It's yours.
It's amazing." Proposed designs. Design
structure. Fantastic. Absolutely
gorgeous. And that's basically the whole
plan of action. Then if we come back
over to our wonderful Claude code, it is
now ready to go ahead and build it. So,
it's even got an SEO plan, trust
signals, content strategy, page
structure, which is awesome. So, now
we're going to head and go ahead and do
it. And once we've done that, we can
then integrate our 3D animated section.
Hey there, dude. That sounds great. Go
ahead and build that initial website at
making sure that we leave a space for me
to give you the video to do the
integrated animated structure uh for the
pool. And then we send them off. And if
you're wondering how I'm doing this, I'm
using Glido as a speech-to-text service.
Basically, you hit a key, you yap, and
then the messages appear. Just saves a
lot of time. Wonderful. So, now we've
got a website SEO optimized and
influenced. So, we've got the homepage
where we're going to have our beautiful
animation. Let's scroll down and see
what we've got. Gorgeous images, free
estimates, five-star service. This
really feels like a premium brand. Cool.
Pool care that protects your investment.
Some great imagery there. Okay, this is
quite tasty. Your neighbor, your pool
guy. This is cool. Pools that transform.
She's got some different ideas and proof
uh six reasons to trust us. Okay, so
this is something that we want to kind
of fix. It's kind of like a grading
thing. But completely fine. First draft,
that's fine. Come down. Trusted by pool
owners. This, by the way, pulls it
directly from the website. So these
should be actual reviews that exist on
Google, which is fantastic. Come down.
Your pool deserves better. Let's make it
happen. Proudly serving in Texas. Lots
of different brands there. And then
ready for pool cleaner. And then we've
got a nice contact form at the bottom
where they can get started. So now we
have an initial overview of the website.
The next step is to take this
interstellar by bringing a beautiful,
show-stopping animation we can add
directly into the website with Nano
Banana 2. Now to do this, I'm heading
back over to Community Scrub to Assets.
I'll put these down below so you can
grab these particular ones. We're going
to look for the 3D website builder. And
then we're also looking for asset
generation. And of course, we're SEO
optimizer. Little side note, by the way,
you do want to be building out your
skills repository of code skills. It's
going to set you up whether you're using
Open Claw or just building out systems.
So, two things we want to download.
Number one is 3D website builder. Let's
come down here and just click on
download this one real quick. And then
we're going to go ahead and download the
second. And then we've got our asset
generator, and let's just download this
one. So once we've downloaded them,
guys, we're going to select both of
these and we're going to drag them over
to our folder. Yes, add folders to
workspace. Beautiful. And we'll open a
brand new thing. If you're using a
terminal, all you do is click on this
plus. Opens up a brand new terminal. You
just come down. You select it, hit
enter, and then you're rocking and
rolling. Then we're going to select the
claw to summon him. Now, let's begin the
entire process. So, hey there, I've just
added two initial skills to the
left-hand side. A 3D website builder and
then I've added a 3D website asset
generator. What I would like you to do
is create two skills in Claude for those
two things. And I'd like to start with a
3D website asset generator. You can tell
what website we're building based on the
information on the left, but I would
like to create for this website a pool
that basically goes from being dirty and
filthy to completely clean. Do this to
build out the gorgeous animation files
for me so I can just copy and paste and
make it look epic. Now, what this will
do actually is generate for us three
different prompts that we're going to
need to use on whatever image generation
we're using to create this beautiful
animation. So whilst this is creating
the asset, let's go over to Higgsfield
to use this. Now, you don't have to use
Higgsfield, but I'm going to use it here
because it's a really easy way to
actually generate some incredible
images. So you're going to go to image
higgsfield.ai. Great. You're going to
sign in and or create an account. So
let's get rid of this guy real quick.
Come over and log in. Continue with
Google. Wonderful. And so now we've got
three prompts. Yours will look exactly
like this cuz you've got the code. We've
got the dirty pool. We've got the
crystal clean pool and then the video
transition. So, let's grab the dirty
pool. Click on copy and cast. You know,
I'm a sucker for my confetti, but we
grab that. Now, let's head over to
Higgsfield. Then, guys, you'll click on
images over here on the left-hand side
and click on create an image and you'll
be here. Now, I've done all of the work
for you in terms of what you actually
need cuz we want a white background. So
we're coming we're going to drop in the
prompt like so, which is fantastic. Now,
dimensions. Make sure that you are at 16
by 9. Quality control, we want it to be
2K. And then the model is going to be
Nano Banana 2, which is fantastic. And
again, just make sure we've got the
right dimensions on there. Make sure the
right quality control is 2K. And then
literally, we want four generations so
we can pick the perfect dirty, neglected
pool. Come over and then click on
generate. Wonderful. So now we've got
some dirty pools. Oh my gosh, guys, look
at this. Are you Are you thirsty? You
thirsty for some pools right now? So you
can pick the one that you want to. I
always recommend at this stage spa that
little bit. Find one that you like. You
want little bits in there. Do you want
those a giraffe in the last video? I
don't know if my edits can pull that up
right now. They disappeared in the any
van. So if you want to add a giraffe in
here, we can make anything happen. So
very, very crazy. Let's pick one that
looks really dirty. Maybe we go for
Yeah, let's go for this one here. This
is particularly
um pungent and doesn't look very nice.
Click on reference. And all we're going
to do now is pretty much delete this
prompt like so and get rid of this guy.
And then we come back over to our
document here. On the crystal clean pool
one, we're just going to copy it. Then
come straight back over and paste it in.
And one thing you'll notice is that the
outskirts are white. This is so that it
will blend perfectly into your website.
One option you have got, if you want, I
want to throw out there so you're aware
of it, is you can go more detail like
this. Like you see how this one, for
example, looks really freaking bad. Like
look at that, how terrible that looks.
So we can play around with that if you
want to so that it's kind of a little
bit more integrated. But you get the
idea. It's essentially how well do you
want it to integrate into the website?
But you can play around with that and
get it so it's absolutely like really
filthy. So you could, for example, come
down here and click on reference. And we
could say something like let's just make
sure that it's a full white border and
cut off the stuff at the bottom. And
then you effectively, once you've given
it some feedback, you get two that you
really like. So I really like this one
here. So this one is so freaking bad,
man. Is this what the average pool owner
in Texas looks like? Maybe you Texans
can let me know. I'd love to come out
there one day. Maybe live. I think it'd
be cool. And then this is the free
version. Cool. The clean. This is after
Diamond Pool Clean Services rock up.
This is just what we do. This is how we
roll. That's what kind of experience we
sell. What we're going to do now is
download this one here. Let's get this
one downloaded onto the computer. And
then we're also going to go ahead and
download this guy right here. Fantastic.
Then we're going to head over on the
left-hand side onto video like so and
click on create a video. And then all
we're going to do, guys, is have your
start frame and you're just going to
basically click on that image. So now
we've got our before photo and then
we're going to have afterwards our after
photo of a beautiful pool. Then we're
going to go ahead and grab a prompt from
our AI, which is over here in video
transition. Just copy this bad boy. Come
back over and then we're going to fit
that into the model like so. Fantastic.
And then you can specify everything you
want to down here. Quality, 5 seconds I
think it's going to be fine for this. We
don't need the audio in this instance
cuz it's not really relevant. And then
we want to do multi-shot shouldn't be
okay. Depends like, you know, you can
play around a little bit. Usually I find
it's quite okay, but you can experiment.
And then click on generate. Now as you
can see the one from before, this was
the any van one with the giraffe. There
he is. People say he disappeared. I
actually think he just went into the van
for a little bit of relaxing, guys. I
think people are too harsh on that
giraffe. He likes to hang out, chill
out, and do what he likes to do.
Wonderful. So now we have the whole
image, which is decent. So let's go
ahead and hit play and see what that one
looks like. Just like that. All
beautiful clean. That's the kind of
effect that we have. And of course, you
can play around with this as much as you
want to. You can just say, for example,
create a beautiful, seamless transition
between the two. Make sure any objects
that are extinct do so in a natural way.
Make it a seamless, beautiful
transition. You can play around with it.
I encourage you to do a few of these
just to make sure that you're happy with
it. Model Clean 3.0 is fine. You can
play around with different models. Of
course, you can. It's really up to you
how you want to play around with it. And
of course, you can up quality if you
want to. It just costs a few more
credits. So we'll try this one with
1080p. Cool. And so I've got a new one
here. And guys, I actually I think going
up a little bit on quality has really
elevated the feel of this and things are
just getting swept away. Things are
falling down. I think it looks a little
bit better. But play around with it.
Create as many different things as you
want to. And when this is answer to
download, we're going to come over here.
We're going to come and grab this guy
like so. And just bring it onto our
computer, which is fantastic. Then we
head over to antigravity. And then once
you've downloaded it, just come over,
grab the file, drop it straight in, and
then we're going to have a and yap to
Claude and just give it the following
prompt. Hey there, so I have just
downloaded a file, a video, and I would
like this to be at the very top of the
website. Now, I want you to integrate it
in such a way that as I scroll down,
basically it looks like an animation.
You need to change the top of the
website to white and you can use this 3D
website builder for best principles in
terms of how to integrate this animate
this sort of like scroll effect. As I
scroll down the website, the pool gets
clean, basically. Beautiful. So here we
go. And by the way, if it doesn't work
the first time, just come back and say,
"Hey dude, I want it to be a little bit
slower, a little bit faster." I've added
the best practices in the skill. But
here's Diamond D Pool Services. We
scroll down. What do we see? And look at
that. This could be your pool. Get a
free estimate. How cool is that? That is
so sick. We come down the website. We've
got everything we had here earlier.
Professional service, maintenance and
repair. Pool care that protects your
investment. We go all the way down the
website looking really slick, really
decent, and we've got everything that we
wanted. Six reasons to trust us. That
basically scroll thing has disappeared.
We've got the reviews on Facebook.
Everything we do. Free to pool cleaner
and a contact form at the bottom. And
then of course, we would just want to
test the mobile optimization cuz guys, I
know we love our tablets. I don't know
who's surfing the web on a tablet in
2026. If that's you, can you let me know
down in the comments? I genuinely I want
to know. But the point is you can see it
scales well. Now, the cool thing about
this image is even if you're on a mobile
or whatever, you can still see the pool
transforming as you come down. You can
see. Beautiful. This pool could be
yours. You don't actually need the
external context on this, which is why
it's great to have an image like this.
So come. And obviously, you can change
it. You can even do one for a mobile
versus a desktop. All you do is repeat
the same process, but make it square. Or
you could make it long long sort of like
a horizontal if you want to. And it'd be
the same kind of process. And all you
say to Claude is just change it when it
hits a certain breakpoint that is
reasonable and that'll come down and
then work well for you. And this is
completely mobile optimized, guys. This
is a really gorgeous gorgeous gorgeous
website that you would be happy to use.
There are a few things we can do in
terms of functionality, which is decent.
And to fix that, we're going to use a
UI/UX pro skill. And to do that, you can
go over to this website here. And what
this effectively is, guys, a lot of
people, okay, that are very big nerds on
UI/UX basically sat together in a room,
I believe, and they built this
incredible thing out, which basically
tests it for hundreds of minute things,
accessibility, design, SEO, you name it,
it's in here. So what we're going to do
now is let you come over. You're going
to copy this code like so. Click on
copy. Head back over to antigravity,
which will pull up at the bottom. And
then effectively, we're going to say the
following. Hey there, I'd like you to
download this skill and do a full audit
of this website for me, making sure that
it is fully SEO optimized and it is
fully accessible based on all the
requirements that are basically
mentioned in this skill installed on the
left-hand side. And once that's done,
just give me a cool checklist of
everything you've done and all the
changes that you've made. As simple as
that. And then drop the URL. Guys, and
just like that, it's done 15 critical
accessibility checks. It's done a skip
link. It's got nav bar sorted out. It's
done so many different things. It's done
eight fixes on SEO, which is fantastic.
It's done various different improvements
on image dimensions, form and feedback,
you know, touch and interaction. You
think about how long it would take you
and I sat down going through this stuff.
This skill's done all that for us, which
I think is freaking crazy. It's also
installed the skill on the left-hand
side. I always recommend that you just
run this as an audit on whatever website
that you're building. So now we have a
beautiful website that is SEO optimized,
looks gorgeous, and has a
scroll-stopping animation on it. The
next problem we have to solve though is
once we give this to a client, how on
earth do they tell us what they want to
change? Maybe they want to change the
copy. How do you actually solve that?
Well, there are actually three ways. Way
number one is they just pay you to do it
and you're on a retainer. That is the
best way. I cover that in my big AI
website masterclass. The second route is
that you build out a full CMS where they
can do changes. Now, that's great cuz I
have autonomy, but if they do something
that breaks the website, that can
complicate it. And then there's a third
option. There's a really interesting
middle ground makes it easy, but also
gives them the ability to make changes
through you. So, the way we would do
this is we build them a page in the same
style as our website, which you can do
with the prompt I'm going to show you in
a second. You can add in their names.
They basically they can fill everything
out like Diamond D, just like this. They
didn't want a design tweak, a bug issue,
new feature, other. It's a really
gorgeous interactive section. This is so
nice, you could even have this on the
website if you wanted to. Click on
about, they could do everything. And
when that's submitted, that goes through
to this on Notion, which is client
requests. And this could just be the
thing that you check every day. Go
through. What do they want? Don't want
X, want Y. And you can give this to
Claude. You can give this to
Anti-Gravity and say every day like go
and check it. What are the changes?
Approve it and build a skill that says
if it's just to do with copy, we let
that go. If it's a structural change,
you can manage it. And now you can
manage all of your clients here on the
left-hand side, all their requests, get
that complete, and it's a complete It
just takes the back and forth of you and
the and the customer way out of your
hands because it all runs down the
background. I've also created for you a
client feedback portal setup guide. They
just feed this to Claude code in the
same chat window. Doesn't need to be the
same chat window, but just give it to
Claude code and it'll go ahead and
develop you one of these things. The
only thing you need to do is give it
your Notion API key. If you don't know
how to do that, just come on the top
right, come down here to connections,
click on develop integration, and on
develop integration, all you're going to
do is create a new integration. You're
going to give it a name, and you're
going to grab an API key. Then once you
give that API key to Claude code, you
can effectively connect that. You just
give it a prompt just by copying this
whole thing I dealt for you here, and
you'll be ready to connect it and have
the whole system ready to rock and roll.
Now, a beautiful website is one thing,
but actually building it with more
detail and hosting it is something
completely different. We're going to
learn that now by watching this video
right here.